A Guide to the Tazewell family papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
- 31 December 1841 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  receipt from Herman and Company to Littleton Waller Tazewell for purchase of boots
- 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  unsigned and undated deed between Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover County of the first part, Hill Carter of Shirley, John N. Tazewell of Norfolk, and James Lyons of Richmond of the second part and creditors of Edmund F. Wickham of the third part-his estate (except what specified) being sold for his debts-deed of trust
- 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell-revenue tax paid to the borough of Norfolk
- 6 January 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John M. Speed in Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell-would like to meet with Tazewell at his convenience today
- 10 January 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John M. Speed in Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-will accept Tazewell's offer to pay the principal of the bond-will also sign bond of indemnity for Tazewell's protection-other bond matters-says that there are slaves being sold in Williamsburg area
- 14 January 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  account of Littleton Waller Tazewell with John Bonsal and company-payment received
- 19 January 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert P. Waller of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding the settlement of the bond-settlement of another account between them
- 20 January 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell account with Robert P. Waller including settlement of bond-receipt from Waller by John M. Speed
- 5 February 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert Anderson of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding the use of books in Wilkinson vs. Harris-rough draft of Tazewell's reply
- 11 March 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  receipt from John N. Tazewell to James Cherry in payment of Cherry's recovery of a runaway slave John
- 20 March 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John S. Bartlett to John N. Tazewell-asks pardon for not calling on John before leaving town-John's mother sent asparagus
- 18 April 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Henry G. Winter assistant secretary for E. Chappell secretary for the Royal Mail Steam Packet to William Gray-glad to hear that Norfolk wants to be a port of call for their ships-will consider-ships draw 17-18 feet of water, if Norfolk safe to enter and exit?
- 7 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  articles of agreement between Jesse J. Simkins and Thomas Jones
- 7 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John N. Tazewell appointed a visitor for VMI
- 7 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  S. P. Lee at Washington to John N. Tazewell-general news-chess-friend going to publish a newspaper-political news-speculation that Calhoun will have the party nomination-naval committee meeting-party that evening-next duty
- 9 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William Gray of the British Consulate in Norfolk to John N. Tazewell, William G. Camp, and Horatio N. Bucktrout-regarding letter from the Royal Mail Steam Packet to Gray of 18 April 1842
- 30 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert P. Waller of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sends the bond of indemnity-also selling Dismal Swamp Canal stock for estate of Major Griffin
- 31 May 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  F. B. Deane Jr. of Richmond to John N. Tazewell at Powhatan Court House-Mr. Mcfarland, one of the trustees of Dean and Cunninghams will wait on John at Powhatan C.H. regarding debt to Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 2 June 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at Richmond-regarding Deane's debt-wants to settle it as soon as possible-earthquakes in West Indies, fire set in Norfolk-also bloodshed in Norfolk-weather
- 23 June 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  F. B. Deane of Richmond to John Tazewell in Richmond-regarding the settlement of his debt to L.W. Tazewell
- 25 June 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  F. B. Deane of Richmond to John Tazewell in Richmond-regarding the settlement of his debt (Deane and Cunningham) to L.W. Tazewell
- 4 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell in White Sulpher Springs-again Deane's debt-Tredegar's role in it-weather-news-congressional apportionment-how it might break down
- 6 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell in White Sulphur Springs-regarding Deane's debt and Tredegar
- 10 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William F. Wickham of Hanover County to John N. Tazewell-their health-lots of rain, damaging crops-health-York canal-will visit LWT by end of year
- 10 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John N. Tazewell at Lexington to Littleton Waller Tazewell-hasn't heard from the family-his duties as a visitor of VMI-his health-possibility of a new convention
- 11 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  account of Littleton Waller Tazewell with William Dey for vests, pants, pantaloons-paid by date given
- 12 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  resolutions of the Tredegar Iron Works concerning debt to LWT owed by Deane and Cunningham and its payment
- 14 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-letters to John-resolutions by Tredegar concerning Deane and Cunningham debt to Tazewell-will wait until the 25th and probably 1 October for payment-weather-damage to crops-p.s. more rain coming
- 14 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to Nicholas Mills of Richmond-copy of letter dated 6 July 1842 to Francis B. Deane that concerns Deane's debt to him and Tredegar's willingness to pick it up-also Tazewell writes Mills about the resolutions Tredegar sent him
- 18 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John Bidwell of the foreign office to William Gray of the British Consulate in Norfolk-asks him to thank Tazewell [John?] and Dr. J. I. Bartlett for the information on indian corn
- 18 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  J. R. Anderson to John N. and Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding Deane's visit to Norfolk to talk to Tazewell-contains Deane's statement
- 23 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William H. Richardson of Richmond to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-military institute VMI
- 26 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  F. B. Deane of Richmond to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-encloses documents regarding the business between Deane and LWT-says LWT fallen into erroneous views and done him an injustice-the debt
- 26 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Benjamin Watkins Leigh of Richmond to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-sale of property to pay debt Deane owes LWT
- 26 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  deed between Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover 1st part, John N. Tazewell of Norfolk and James M. Wickham of Richmond of the 2nd part, and William F. Wickham of Hanover 3rd part-deed of trust to Tazewell and J. M. Wickham to indemnify William F. Wickham
- 26 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-correspondence between the two-sent note to Leigh asking him to put notice in paper for trust sale and not to give an extension to Tredegar-believes Tredegar might stop sale by finally making the payment-damage from rains and storm-may not be so bad-no news on John's plantation-Eastern Shore crops-family's health-news of neighbors-p.s.-news of Lambert's crops-rain
- 28 July 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sale of his brother's estate for payment of debt-his indemnity in the matter
- 7 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-going to Eastern Shore-Deane debt-matters of another gentleman whose brother asks advice (Wickhams?)-weather
- 8 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-his business affairs
- 15 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-the Deane debt and Tredegar-advertisement for sale in paper-Eastern Shore plantations-John's plantation
- 15 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Daniel A. Wilson of Cumberland County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-understands Tazewell having a considerable debt to be paid to him-would he be interested in loaning some of it out-has a friend who could use a loan if so disposed-has some good land along the James River in Buckingham County-politics-Tazewell's work on monied institutions-will he be in Richmond for the general court
- 22 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  account of Mary Tazewell with M. A. Butt for ribbon etc-paid
- 28 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-hurricane passed through-much rain-John's plantation damaged-Lambert gave John's brother $60 for the fishery-Gardiner back, doesn't know how report of his "death" started-Clark's nomination before Senate-Edmund Wickham's affairs-John's slaves
- 29 August 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  account of Littleton Waller Tazewell with E. Decormis for whiskey-paid
- 4 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-John's health-John's plantation-chess-situation between Norfolk chess club and NY chess club-no news can't find in newspapers-guns fired in salute to the president's arrival in the harbor-p.s. gives the club's chess situation-report that president arrived erroneous-fired for some other reason
- 12 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell at White Sulphur Springs-writing John letters-John's anxiety over a family member unwarranted-condition of family, crops, and gardens-recent storm and damage from it-John's plantation-thinks when John comes home he should stop in Richmond for Tredegar sale, rather than come home and go back-p.s. Tazewell's health
- 19 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell expected in Charlottesville-Tazewell's health-weather-Tredegar business-Lambert and John's fishery
- 20 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert Johnston at White Sulphur Springs to John N. Tazewell at Hot Springs-their friend Will is doing much better
- 21 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert Johnston at White Sulphur Springs to John N. Tazewell at Hot Springs-Will's health-plans to leave White Sulphur and catch up to Tazewell-other news
- 22 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert Johnston at White Sulphur Springs to John N. Tazewell at Hot Springs-can't buy much water-Will's health-Springs nearly deserted
- 25 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell expected in Richmond-Tazewell's health-not going to say anything about Deane's debt in letter but requesting that John come home so they can discuss it before he goes back to Richmond-family's health-Norfolk's climate
- 27 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Robert Johnston at White Sulphur Springs to John N. Tazewell at Warm Springs-had to hurry back to White Sulpher Springs to take care of a patient-won't be able to meet up with Tazewell
- 27 September 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-his financial condition-crops
- 3 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell in Richmond-not disappointed to not see John-eventually figured would be impossible for him to get to Norfolk by the 30th-Tazewell's health-Deane's debt-possibility of John purchasing some slaves-possibility of purchasing a landed estate-locations of lands that Tazewell might like-a possible summer retreat-got better porter when he lived in Richmond than he does in Norfolk-other news-p.s. Tredegar trying to postpone sale, Tazewell disinclinged to do anything for them-says John handling the business of it-Edmund Wickham-Wescoatt's health, Tazewell's health-visit with the president-nice chat, but nothing special-Littleton Jr. saw Lambert concerning the fishery-shoes for Tazewell's slaves have shown up
- 4 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell in Richmond-regarding Cunningham's debt (which is also Deane's debt and involves Tredegar)-potential avenues for John to pursue at his discretion-possibly meeting with Edmund Wickham-check into the sale of any estates-Tazewell's health-maybe going over to Eastern Shore
- 8 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-asks for help in getting an appointment to West Point
- 11 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John M. Gregory acting governor to John N. Tazewell-finally has an answer from the attorney general regarding John's letter of 4 May-includes opinion of attorney general on right of the state proxies to vote for directors of banks
- 13 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Tazewell Taylor in Richmond to John N. Tazewell-sorry he missed Tazewell in Richmond-possibility of a loan from LWT
- 20 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-very thankful for Tazewell's letter-sending Tazewell's letter to Tyler without any additional comments-West Point application
- 22 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William H. Richardson of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-thanks him for loan of $5 to his son-in Amelia County when John was in Richmond-regards to family
- 24 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell at Old Plantation to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-wants John to have items (posts, studding, plates) sent over-Smith can pick them if still in Norfolk-if not Aaron Mihado can do (Mihado the supplier)
- 25 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William Fox-account with Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 31 October 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell Wickham of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-received his letter-tried forwarding it to his brother-other matters
- 1 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William H. Cabell of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-letter of introduction for Charles A. Scott-Scott's property
- 5 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-thanks him for his letter-Wickham's age, stature, physical well-being-walked 12 miles in under 3 hours
- 8 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  John M. Speed of Lynchburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-apologizes for bothering Tazewell-asks for a loan
- 9 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  William F. Wickham of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-informs Tazewell that he should come to his Hanover plantation-bid on James River estates-wishes he could come to Norfolk but too much business
- 13 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sale of his property
- 24 November 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  sale of slaves of Edmund F. Wickham ordered by John N. Tazewell and James M. Wickham, trustees-gives names of purchasers and slaves, and price
- 10 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Edmund F. Wickham of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-asks him to send letter to him at Richmond
- 10 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  James Lyons of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-putting sale of Rocky Mills on hold until hears from John about the sale
- 17 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Edmund F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding his letter to John and his debt
- 18 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  James Lyons of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-regarding Wickham's request for postponement of sale of Rocky Mills
- 20 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  E. G. Austin of Boston to Littleton Waller Tazewell-copy of a document stating that James B. Gray had given up his claim to George Latimer being his slave-indemnifies Gray from any legal challenges
- 29 December 1842 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Claudius Crozet in Richmond to John N. Tazewell-discussion of a chess match-other news
- 1842 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Wilkinson vs. Harris' estate-legal papers
- 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  receipt from Sally Fox to William H[?] for $10.32 for weaving cloth
- 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  tax receipt to Littleton Waller Tazewell for taxes paid to Norfolk County
- 2 January 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Gustavus A. Myers of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-health of James Wickham
- 8 January 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  John N. Tazewell in Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-business matters including Edmund Wickham's property
- 12 January 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  James Lyons to John N. Tazewell-asks Tazewell to pass letters to George Loyall
- 18 January 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  William Selden, Treasurer of the U.S. to John N. Tazewell-sends treasury notes for draft-always glad to help John and his father
- February 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  receipt from Sally Fox to Old Plantation for payment for work
- February 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  receipt from Yerby Evans, and Kelly to William Wescoatt for payment for work collars for Old Plantation
- 13 February 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  deed between William S. Floyd and Ann Floyd of Northampton County and Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk-selling Tazewell a tract of land-proven in Northampton County Court 13 February 1843
- 14 February 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  William S. Floyd at Tom[?] Fields to John N. Tazewell-schools in Northampton County
- 24 February 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Francis Mallory to John N. Tazewell-asks for his help for Mr. Blanchard a miniature portraitist
- March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  receipt from William G. Sands, clerk of the Superior Court of Chancery for the District of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell in payment for continuance
- 5 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  James Porter of Iberville, Louisiana to John N. Tazewell- thanks for plans for Baltimore Cottages-sorry hasn't been better correspondent-chess match-brother (Alexander Porter) elected to Senate despite his wishes-will visit Norfolk on next trip to VA
- 7 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  appointment of John N. Tazewell as a visitor for VMI by Governor James McDowell
- 7 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  William F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-business transaction with Genl. Pegram and Mr. Harrison
- 18 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  A. S. Hitselberger of Norfolk to council of the Norfolk Lyceum-will speak to the Lyceum on the crusades at the end of May
- 20 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  ticket for the Lyceum to John N. Tazewell-signed by Tazewell as president and M. Fitzgibbon as treasurer-cost $5
- 21 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  William F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sent his bond to Tazewell for the sum remitted to Genl. Pegram to Wickham's credit in the Bank of Virginia-debt to Mr. Harrison paid-weather-current economic difficulties-possibility of war-chess
- 28 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  A. S. Hitselberger to Littleton Waller Tazewell-thanks Tazewell for legal advice for Lt. O'Brien-sending Tazewell O'Brien's intended defense asking Tazewell to look at it-gives Catholic Church's position
- 29 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Nicholas Mills, president of Tredegar Iron works to John N. Tazewell-sending interest payment on bond
- 29 March 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  William N. Mercer of New Orleans to John N. Tazewell-weather for trip home-economic conditions in New Orleans-election of Porter to the Senate-other news
- 4 April 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  M. Mckennie of Lexington to John N. Tazewell-selected by the society of alumni of VMI to address it at their next meeting
- 20 April 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  commissioner Anderson's office in Williamsburg-report regarding Wilkinson vs. Harris
- 20 April 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-has not yet heard about his application to West Point
- May 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell et al to the clerk of Princess Anne County Court for entering decree in suit against Kemp
- 2 May 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  list of debts due by Edmund F. Wickham which Messers. Tazewell and Lyons will settle
- 7 May 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell in Richmond-asks John to meet him in Williamsburg if not at Grove Landing
- 20 May 1843 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  hire of slaves between 1803 and 1820-suit of Wilkinson vs. Harris
- 2 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account of sale of the silver plate of the estate of Edmund Wickham by order of James Lyons and John N. Tazewell
- 3 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from Thomas J. Dororty [sp.] to William H. Wescoat for payment for work done on wind mill
- 8 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account of James Lyons and John N. Tazewell, trustees for Edmund F. Wickham with Inloes and Brother
- 16 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  D. H. Mahan at West Point NY to John N. Tazewell-young Shields-other news and gossip and reminiscences
- 18 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account and receipt for William Fox for board
- 20 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  William H. Richardson of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-asks him to take a package
- 21 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  William R. Galt of Williamsburg to John N. Tazewell-Norfolk Academy-will not work at academy unless his friend Mr. Pryor is made president with authority to appoint associate teachers-pushes for Pryor
- 23 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from William M. Ames to William H. Wescoat for payment of $27 for repair on windmill
- 23 June 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from George Robins to William H. Wescoat for settlement of accounts against Old Plantation
- 1 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  statement-James Lyons-John Tazewell no longer a trustee for Edmund F. Wickham-Lyons solely responsible
- 1 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from William D. Mitchell to William H. Wescoat for payment of $29.37 1/2 for work at Old Plantation
- 11 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell account with Joseph Nottingham-pays for services rendered by wife to one of the slaves at King's Creek
- 14 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account with Tully Drighouse for mowing
- 16 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Robert Johnston of White Sulpher Springs to John N. Tazewell-heard that John was sick and his brother was escorting his sisters to the springs-this season
- 17 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from William D. Mitchell to William H. Wescoat for payment of $5.62 1/2 for work done at New Quarter
- 17 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from William D. Mitchell to William H. Wescoat for payment of $4.37 1/2 for work done at Old Plantation
- 18 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  note that Minny Douty cutting oats for Mr. Joynes and will be paid by William Wescoat
- 22 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Benjamin Watkins Leigh of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-has the "Tyler-grippe" or influenza-will go to Williamsburg to argue case, but wonders if it is necessary-believes proper documentation about all one can do before the circuit superior court
- 27 July 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Charles Dimmock of Richmond to John N. Tazewell-concerning a matter with Captain Ericsson
- August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account of William Fox (for Littleton Waller Tazewell) with James B. Dolby for repairing scythes, wheels-paid
- 7 August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Thomas O. Cogbill of Williamsburg to Littleton Waller Tazewell-received his letter-Cogbill ill and not in office for a while-when gets back will transmit record of Wilkinson vs. Harris
- 9 August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  George M. Tazewell of Canterbury England to Littleton Waller Tazewell-information on the Tazewell family in the 16-17-18 centuries in England
- 11 August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  receipt from E. W. Nottingham and Company to William Wescoat for payment for cotton cards and wool cards
- 12 August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  account of William Wescoat with Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 15 August 1843 (Box 8, Folder 5)